<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Solar System</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">Sun</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">Mercury</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Venus</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Earth</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">Mars</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Asteroid belt</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">Saturn</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Uranus</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">Neptune</string>
    <string name="affirmation11">Kuiper belt</string>
    <string name="affirmation12">Oort cloud</string>

    <string name="affirmation1_1">The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System.
        It is a nearly perfect ball of hot plasma, heated to incandescence by
        nuclear fusion reactions in its core. The Sun radiates this energy mainly as light,
        ultraviolet, and infrared radiation, and is the most important source of energy
        for life on Earth.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2_1">Mercury is the first planet from the Sun and the
        smallest planet in the Solar System. It is a terrestrial planet with a heavily
        cratered surface due to the planet having no geological activity and an extremely
        tenuous atmosphere (called an exosphere).</string>
    <string name="affirmation3_1">Venus is the second planet from the Sun. It is a rocky
        planet with the densest atmosphere of all the rocky bodies in the Solar System,
        and the only one with a mass and size that is close to that of its orbital neighbour
        Earth. Orbiting inferiorly (inside of Earth\'s orbit), it appears in Earth\'s sky
        always close to the Sun, as either a "morning star" or an "evening star".</string>
    <string name="affirmation4_1">Earth is the third planet from the Sun and the only
        place known in the universe where life has originated and found habitability.
        Earth is a water world, the only one in the Solar System to sustain liquid
        surface water. Its ocean covers 70.8% of its crust and contains almost all of its
        water. Most other water is retained in Earth\'s large polar sheets of ice, covering
        ocean and land, dwarfing Earth\'s groundwater, lakes, rivers and atmospheric water.
        The other 29.2% of the Earth\'s surface is land, consisting of continents and
        islands, and is widely covered by vegetation.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5_1">Mars is the fourth planet and the furthest terrestrial
        planet from the Sun. The reddish color of its surface is due to finely grained
        iron(III) oxide dust in the soil, giving it the nickname "the Red Planet". Mars\’s
        radius is second smallest among the planets in the Solar System. Mars has two
        irregularly shaped natural
        satellites: Phobos and Deimos.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6_1">The asteroid belt is a torus-shaped region in the Solar
        System, centered on the Sun and roughly spanning the space between the orbits
        of the planets Jupiter and Mars. It contains a great many solid, irregularly
        shaped bodies called asteroids or minor planets. The identified objects are of many
        sizes, but much smaller than planets, and on average are about one million
        kilometers apart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7_1">Jupiter is the fifth planet from the Sun and the largest
        in the Solar System. It is a gas giant with a mass more than two and a half times
        that of all the other planets in the Solar System combined, and slightly less
        than one one-thousandth the mass of the Sun. Jupiter is the third brightest natural
        object in the Earth\'s night sky after the Moon and Venus. Jupiter forms a system
        of 95 known moons and
        probably many more.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8_1">Saturn is the sixth planet from the Sun and the
        second-largest in the Solar System, after Jupiter. The planet has a
        prominent ring system, which is composed mainly of ice particles, with a smaller
        amount of rocky debris and dust. At least 146 moons are known to orbit the planet,
        of which 63 are officially named, this does not include the hundreds of moonlets
        in its rings.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9_1">Uranus is the seventh planet from the Sun and is a gaseous
        cyan ice giant. Most of the planet is made out of water, ammonia, and methane in a
        supercritical phase of matter, which in astronomy is called \'ice\' or volatiles.
        The planet\'s atmosphere has a complex layered cloud structure and has the lowest
        minimum temperature of 49 K (−224 °C) out of all Solar System\'s planets.
        The Uranian axis of rotation is approximately parallel with the plane
        of the Solar System</string>
    <string name="affirmation10_1">Neptune is the eighth planet from the Sun and the farthest
        known planet in the Solar System. It is the fourth-largest planet in the Solar
        System by diameter, the third-most-massive planet, and the densest giant planet.
        Being composed primarily of gases and liquids, it has no well-defined solid surface.
        The planet orbits the Sun once every 164.8 years at an average distance of 30.1
        astronomical units (4.5 billion kilometres).</string>
    <string name="affirmation11_1">The Kuiper belt is a circumstellar disc in the outer
        Solar System, extending from the orbit of Neptune at 30 astronomical units (AU)
        to approximately 50 AU from the Sun.[2] It is similar to the asteroid belt, but
        is far larger—20 times as wide and 20–200 times as massive. Like the asteroid belt,
        it consists mainly of small bodies or remnants from when the Solar System formed.
        While many asteroids are composed primarily of rock and metal, most Kuiper belt
        objects are composed largely of frozen volatiles (termed "ices"), such as methane,
        ammonia, and water.</string>
    <string name="affirmation12_1">The Oort cloud is theorized to be a vast cloud composed
        mainly of icy planetesimals surrounding the Sun at distances ranging from 2,000 to
        200,000 AU (0.03 to 3.2 light-years). The cloud is thought to comprise two regions:
        a disc-shaped inner Oort cloud aligned with the solar ecliptic and a spherical
        outer Oort cloud enclosing the entire solar system. Both regions lie well beyond
        the heliosphere and are in interstellar space.</string>
</resources>